{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985959853","data":{"timestamp":" 947985959852"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985960078","data":{"timestamp":" 947985960077"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985961040","data":{"timestamp":" 947985961040"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985962313","data":{"timestamp":" 947985962312"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985965203","data":{"timestamp":" 947985965202"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985966045","data":{"timestamp":" 947985966045"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985966357","data":{"timestamp":" 947985966357"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985967590","data":{"timestamp":" 947985967590"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985971062","data":{"timestamp":" 947985971062"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985972045","data":{"timestamp":" 947985972045"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985972298","data":{"timestamp":" 947985972298"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985973241","data":{"timestamp":" 947985973241"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985976079","data":{"timestamp":" 947985976079"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985977111","data":{"timestamp":" 947985977111"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985977583","data":{"timestamp":" 947985977583"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985982083","data":{"timestamp":" 947985982083"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985982143","data":{"timestamp":" 947985982143"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2ee80f4a-ea55-437e-b759-a0ee18d47473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985991859","data":{"timestamp":" 947985991859"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985992473","data":{"timestamp":" 947985992473"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985993536","data":{"timestamp":" 947985993536"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985994258","data":{"timestamp":" 947985994257"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985995190","data":{"timestamp":" 947985995189"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUNA"," userResponse":" ALIVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985995996","data":{"timestamp":" 947985995996"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985996668","data":{"timestamp":" 947985996667"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUU"," userResponse":" VIKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985997370","data":{"timestamp":" 947985997369"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" SHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947985997965","data":{"timestamp":" 947985997964"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986000995","data":{"timestamp":" 947986000995"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIPENDEZA"," userResponse":" VILIPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986001209","data":{"timestamp":" 947986001208"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986002192","data":{"timestamp":" 947986002192"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986002916","data":{"timestamp":" 947986002916"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986003509","data":{"timestamp":" 947986003509"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986006521","data":{"timestamp":" 947986006521"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVICHOMA"," userResponse":" ALIVICHOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986007714","data":{"timestamp":" 947986007714"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" TARATIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986008637","data":{"timestamp":" 947986008637"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986009420","data":{"timestamp":" 947986009420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986009814","data":{"timestamp":" 947986009813"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986010727","data":{"timestamp":" 947986010727"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986011320","data":{"timestamp":" 947986011320"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986014542","data":{"timestamp":" 947986014542"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986014706","data":{"timestamp":" 947986014706"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986015669","data":{"timestamp":" 947986015668"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986016640","data":{"timestamp":" 947986016639"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986017475","data":{"timestamp":" 947986017475"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITIA"," userResponse":" AKITIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986018179","data":{"timestamp":" 947986018179"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TONGE"," userResponse":" TONGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986018364","data":{"timestamp":" 947986018364"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986018920","data":{"timestamp":" 947986018919"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986020013","data":{"timestamp":" 947986020012"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWANI"," userResponse":" KINYWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986021216","data":{"timestamp":" 947986021216"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986021640","data":{"timestamp":" 947986021640"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986022694","data":{"timestamp":" 947986022694"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIBISHWA"," userResponse":" ULIBISHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986025196","data":{"timestamp":" 947986025196"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986026100","data":{"timestamp":" 947986026100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986026914","data":{"timestamp":" 947986026914"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOYONI"," userResponse":" MOYONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986029492","data":{"timestamp":" 947986029492"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986029965","data":{"timestamp":" 947986029965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986030679","data":{"timestamp":" 947986030679"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWEZA"," userResponse":" ANAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986031053","data":{"timestamp":" 947986031053"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986031969","data":{"timestamp":" 947986031969"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986034472","data":{"timestamp":" 947986034472"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986035623","data":{"timestamp":" 947986035622"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFUNGUA"," userResponse":" AKAFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986036322","data":{"timestamp":" 947986036322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986038672","data":{"timestamp":" 947986038672"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa aliyeonekana mchovu alisimama mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986040086","data":{"timestamp":" 947986040085"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa aliyeonekana mchovu alisimama mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEONEKANA"," userResponse":" ALIYEONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986040886","data":{"timestamp":" 947986040885"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa aliyeonekana mchovu alisimama mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOVU"," userResponse":" MCHOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986042340","data":{"timestamp":" 947986042340"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa aliyeonekana mchovu alisimama mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986043254","data":{"timestamp":" 947986043254"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa aliyeonekana mchovu alisimama mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGONI"," userResponse":" MLANGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986045642","data":{"timestamp":" 947986045642"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa akamwambia Anansi Tafadhali niruhusu niingie."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986046926","data":{"timestamp":" 947986046926"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa akamwambia Anansi Tafadhali niruhusu niingie."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" AKAMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986047520","data":{"timestamp":" 947986047519"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa akamwambia Anansi Tafadhali niruhusu niingie."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986048903","data":{"timestamp":" 947986048903"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa akamwambia Anansi Tafadhali niruhusu niingie."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986049716","data":{"timestamp":" 947986049716"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa akamwambia Anansi Tafadhali niruhusu niingie."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIRUHUSU"," userResponse":" NIRUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986050520","data":{"timestamp":" 947986050520"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa akamwambia Anansi Tafadhali niruhusu niingie."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIINGIE"," userResponse":" NIINGIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986053483","data":{"timestamp":" 947986053483"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina uchovu mwingi na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMETEMBEA"," userResponse":" NIMETEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986054098","data":{"timestamp":" 947986054097"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina uchovu mwingi na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENDO"," userResponse":" MWENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986054917","data":{"timestamp":" 947986054916"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina uchovu mwingi na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986055370","data":{"timestamp":" 947986055370"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina uchovu mwingi na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986057644","data":{"timestamp":" 947986057644"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina uchovu mwingi na njaa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986058738","data":{"timestamp":" 947986058738"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina uchovu mwingi na njaa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHOVU"," userResponse":" UCHOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986059632","data":{"timestamp":" 947986059632"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina uchovu mwingi na njaa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGI"," userResponse":" MWINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986060076","data":{"timestamp":" 947986060075"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina uchovu mwingi na njaa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986060871","data":{"timestamp":" 947986060871"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina uchovu mwingi na njaa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986063783","data":{"timestamp":" 947986063783"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilimbidi Anansi amruhusu aingie ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMBIDI"," userResponse":" ILIMBIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986064486","data":{"timestamp":" 947986064486"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilimbidi Anansi amruhusu aingie ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986065499","data":{"timestamp":" 947986065499"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilimbidi Anansi amruhusu aingie ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMRUHUSU"," userResponse":" AMRUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986066292","data":{"timestamp":" 947986066292"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilimbidi Anansi amruhusu aingie ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AINGIE"," userResponse":" AINGIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986067056","data":{"timestamp":" 947986067056"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilimbidi Anansi amruhusu aingie ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986070157","data":{"timestamp":" 947986070156"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986070911","data":{"timestamp":" 947986070910"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986071734","data":{"timestamp":" 947986071734"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986072477","data":{"timestamp":" 947986072477"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOYO"," userResponse":" MCHOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986073060","data":{"timestamp":" 947986073060"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986076706","data":{"timestamp":" 947986076705"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANGEMGAWIA"," userResponse":" HANGEMGAWIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986077259","data":{"timestamp":" 947986077259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986077933","data":{"timestamp":" 947986077933"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986078657","data":{"timestamp":" 947986078657"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986079131","data":{"timestamp":" 947986079131"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986079874","data":{"timestamp":" 947986079874"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMU"," userResponse":" KITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986080729","data":{"timestamp":" 947986080729"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986081333","data":{"timestamp":" 947986081333"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986083443","data":{"timestamp":" 947986083443"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986084297","data":{"timestamp":" 947986084297"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986085360","data":{"timestamp":" 947986085360"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANGA"," userResponse":" ALIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986086014","data":{"timestamp":" 947986086014"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAMA"," userResponse":" NJAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986086668","data":{"timestamp":" 947986086668"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alipanga njama mbaya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986088937","data":{"timestamp":" 947986088937"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986090141","data":{"timestamp":" 947986090141"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKETI"," userResponse":" ALIPOKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986090335","data":{"timestamp":" 947986090335"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986091069","data":{"timestamp":" 947986091069"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAKA"," userResponse":" KUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986091894","data":{"timestamp":" 947986091894"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986092448","data":{"timestamp":" 947986092448"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986092951","data":{"timestamp":" 947986092951"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986093646","data":{"timestamp":" 947986093645"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986094139","data":{"timestamp":" 947986094139"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUU"," userResponse":" VIKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986095574","data":{"timestamp":" 947986095573"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986096838","data":{"timestamp":" 947986096838"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMKEMEA"," userResponse":" ALIMKEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986097913","data":{"timestamp":" 947986097913"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986098867","data":{"timestamp":" 947986098867"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986099391","data":{"timestamp":" 947986099391"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUONI"," userResponse":" HUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986099965","data":{"timestamp":" 947986099965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986100350","data":{"timestamp":" 947986100350"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986100515","data":{"timestamp":" 947986100515"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986101259","data":{"timestamp":" 947986101259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa alipoketi na kutaka kuanza kula vile viazi vikuu Anansi alimkemea Kasa kwani huoni mikono yako ni michafu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MICHAFU"," userResponse":" MICHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986103766","data":{"timestamp":" 947986103766"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukanawe kwanza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWEZI"," userResponse":" HUWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986104159","data":{"timestamp":" 947986104159"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukanawe kwanza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986104332","data":{"timestamp":" 947986104332"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukanawe kwanza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986104776","data":{"timestamp":" 947986104776"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukanawe kwanza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986105549","data":{"timestamp":" 947986105549"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukanawe kwanza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MICHAFU"," userResponse":" MICHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986107931","data":{"timestamp":" 947986107931"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukanawe kwanza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENDA"," userResponse":" NENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986108384","data":{"timestamp":" 947986108384"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukanawe kwanza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKANAWE"," userResponse":" UKANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986109027","data":{"timestamp":" 947986109027"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukanawe kwanza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986111037","data":{"timestamp":" 947986111036"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986111669","data":{"timestamp":" 947986111669"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986112453","data":{"timestamp":" 947986112453"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986112617","data":{"timestamp":" 947986112617"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986113190","data":{"timestamp":" 947986113190"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986113845","data":{"timestamp":" 947986113845"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986114735","data":{"timestamp":" 947986114735"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MICHAFU"," userResponse":" MICHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986115210","data":{"timestamp":" 947986115209"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986115981","data":{"timestamp":" 947986115981"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986116775","data":{"timestamp":" 947986116775"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986117798","data":{"timestamp":" 947986117798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEITUMIA"," userResponse":" AMEITUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986118982","data":{"timestamp":" 947986118981"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986119595","data":{"timestamp":" 947986119594"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986120046","data":{"timestamp":" 947986120045"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kweli mikono ya Kasa ilikuwa michafu sana kwani alikuwa ameitumia kutembea siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986122195","data":{"timestamp":" 947986122195"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986122979","data":{"timestamp":" 947986122978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986123773","data":{"timestamp":" 947986123773"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986125277","data":{"timestamp":" 947986125277"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIKOKOTA"," userResponse":" ALIJIKOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986126221","data":{"timestamp":" 947986126221"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986127045","data":{"timestamp":" 947986127044"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986127868","data":{"timestamp":" 947986127868"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKANAWA"," userResponse":" AKANAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986128471","data":{"timestamp":" 947986128471"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986128964","data":{"timestamp":" 947986128964"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986131571","data":{"timestamp":" 947986131571"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986133065","data":{"timestamp":" 947986133065"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIKOKOTA"," userResponse":" AKAJIKOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986133629","data":{"timestamp":" 947986133629"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986134743","data":{"timestamp":" 947986134743"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUDI"," userResponse":" AKARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986135087","data":{"timestamp":" 947986135087"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986135891","data":{"timestamp":" 947986135891"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi mezani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZANI"," userResponse":" MEZANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986139029","data":{"timestamp":" 947986139029"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alibaki akibugia viazi kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986139962","data":{"timestamp":" 947986139962"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alibaki akibugia viazi kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBAKI"," userResponse":" ALIBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986141100","data":{"timestamp":" 947986141100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alibaki akibugia viazi kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIBUGIA"," userResponse":" AKIBUGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986141703","data":{"timestamp":" 947986141703"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alibaki akibugia viazi kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986142046","data":{"timestamp":" 947986142046"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alibaki akibugia viazi kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986142999","data":{"timestamp":" 947986142999"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alibaki akibugia viazi kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986145355","data":{"timestamp":" 947986145355"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa aliporejea hakupata kiazi hata kimoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986146519","data":{"timestamp":" 947986146518"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa aliporejea hakupata kiazi hata kimoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOREJEA"," userResponse":" ALIPOREJEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986147991","data":{"timestamp":" 947986147991"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa aliporejea hakupata kiazi hata kimoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUPATA"," userResponse":" HAKUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986148624","data":{"timestamp":" 947986148624"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa aliporejea hakupata kiazi hata kimoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIAZI"," userResponse":" KIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986149447","data":{"timestamp":" 947986149447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa aliporejea hakupata kiazi hata kimoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986150091","data":{"timestamp":" 947986150090"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kasa aliporejea hakupata kiazi hata kimoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMOJA"," userResponse":" KIMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986152368","data":{"timestamp":" 947986152367"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986153991","data":{"timestamp":" 947986153991"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986154574","data":{"timestamp":" 947986154574"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986155438","data":{"timestamp":" 947986155437"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986156938","data":{"timestamp":" 947986156937"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASANTE"," userResponse":" ASANTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986157209","data":{"timestamp":" 947986157209"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986158242","data":{"timestamp":" 947986158242"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIALIKA"," userResponse":" KUNIALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986158466","data":{"timestamp":" 947986158465"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986159039","data":{"timestamp":" 947986159039"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986159293","data":{"timestamp":" 947986159293"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986160096","data":{"timestamp":" 947986160096"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986162669","data":{"timestamp":" 947986162669"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986163202","data":{"timestamp":" 947986163202"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986164895","data":{"timestamp":" 947986164895"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAKUKARIBISHA"," userResponse":" NAKUKARIBISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986165738","data":{"timestamp":" 947986165738"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPITIE"," userResponse":" UPITIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986166282","data":{"timestamp":" 947986166281"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986166724","data":{"timestamp":" 947986166724"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986167288","data":{"timestamp":" 947986167288"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986168143","data":{"timestamp":" 947986168143"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986168567","data":{"timestamp":" 947986168567"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986169641","data":{"timestamp":" 947986169641"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUANDALIE"," userResponse":" NIKUANDALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986170226","data":{"timestamp":" 947986170225"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986171227","data":{"timestamp":" 947986171226"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami pia nakukaribisha upitie kwangu siku moja ili nami nikuandalie chakula kitamu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMU"," userResponse":" KITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986174240","data":{"timestamp":" 947986174239"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Kasa akaanza kujikokota kuelekea kwake nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986175037","data":{"timestamp":" 947986175036"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Kasa akaanza kujikokota kuelekea kwake nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986175886","data":{"timestamp":" 947986175886"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Kasa akaanza kujikokota kuelekea kwake nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986177277","data":{"timestamp":" 947986177276"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Kasa akaanza kujikokota kuelekea kwake nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIKOKOTA"," userResponse":" KUJIKOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986178367","data":{"timestamp":" 947986178366"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Kasa akaanza kujikokota kuelekea kwake nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUELEKEA"," userResponse":" KUELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986178864","data":{"timestamp":" 947986178864"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Kasa akaanza kujikokota kuelekea kwake nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986179655","data":{"timestamp":" 947986179655"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Kasa akaanza kujikokota kuelekea kwake nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986182578","data":{"timestamp":" 947986182577"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986182835","data":{"timestamp":" 947986182834"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986183370","data":{"timestamp":" 947986183369"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986184125","data":{"timestamp":" 947986184124"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KADHAA"," userResponse":" KADHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986185207","data":{"timestamp":" 947986185206"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986186392","data":{"timestamp":" 947986186391"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986187287","data":{"timestamp":" 947986187286"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986188222","data":{"timestamp":" 947986188221"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986188824","data":{"timestamp":" 947986188824"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986190029","data":{"timestamp":" 947986190028"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAHIDI"," userResponse":" ALIMWAHIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986190954","data":{"timestamp":" 947986190953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986191262","data":{"timestamp":" 947986191262"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986191755","data":{"timestamp":" 947986191755"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BURE"," userResponse":" BURE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986194857","data":{"timestamp":" 947986194857"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986195630","data":{"timestamp":" 947986195630"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986196389","data":{"timestamp":" 947986196389"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986197053","data":{"timestamp":" 947986197052"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986198686","data":{"timestamp":" 947986198685"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTEMBELEA"," userResponse":" ALIMTEMBELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986199234","data":{"timestamp":" 947986199233"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986200185","data":{"timestamp":" 947986200185"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986200774","data":{"timestamp":" 947986200774"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo siku moja alimtembelea Kasa nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986203367","data":{"timestamp":" 947986203366"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye Kasa alijilaza chali akiota jua kama Kasa wafanyavyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986203781","data":{"timestamp":" 947986203780"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naye Kasa alijilaza chali akiota jua kama Kasa wafanyavyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986203861","data":{"timestamp":" 947986203861"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 2d3e4e93-9ca9-4dc2-b52b-01a98ff7b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye Kasa alijilaza chali akiota jua kama Kasa wafanyavyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986217972","data":{"timestamp":" 947986217971"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_m-j-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986223221","data":{"timestamp":" 947986223221"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_m-j-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986228774","data":{"timestamp":" 947986228773"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_m-j-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986239179","data":{"timestamp":" 947986239178"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-t-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986243081","data":{"timestamp":" 947986243081"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_h-d-j"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986246533","data":{"timestamp":" 947986246533"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-v-m"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986250205","data":{"timestamp":" 947986250205"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_v-p-j"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986253989","data":{"timestamp":" 947986253989"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_s-j-t"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986257501","data":{"timestamp":" 947986257500"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_k-y-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986262127","data":{"timestamp":" 947986262127"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-b-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986265682","data":{"timestamp":" 947986265681"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_s-j-a"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986269705","data":{"timestamp":" 947986269704"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-e-k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986275478","data":{"timestamp":" 947986275478"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5e97d172-3826-4d18-b39c-352a1bb58ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-e-k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986290041","data":{"timestamp":" 947986290041"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-1-10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986295239","data":{"timestamp":" 947986295239"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986300974","data":{"timestamp":" 947986300974"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986307348","data":{"timestamp":" 947986307348"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986319513","data":{"timestamp":" 947986319513"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-10-15"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986328011","data":{"timestamp":" 947986328011"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986336341","data":{"timestamp":" 947986336341"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986342519","data":{"timestamp":" 947986342519"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986347599","data":{"timestamp":" 947986347599"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986352842","data":{"timestamp":" 947986352841"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-11-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986359122","data":{"timestamp":" 947986359122"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-11-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986364876","data":{"timestamp":" 947986364876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986404008","data":{"timestamp":" 947986404008"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986409493","data":{"timestamp":" 947986409493"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 5fad707e-d2eb-453f-befb-1c2ab5e952ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986420194","data":{"timestamp":" 947986420193"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986420808","data":{"timestamp":" 947986420808"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986421011","data":{"timestamp":" 947986421011"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986421574","data":{"timestamp":" 947986421574"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986422608","data":{"timestamp":" 947986422608"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986422851","data":{"timestamp":" 947986422851"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986423665","data":{"timestamp":" 947986423664"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986424088","data":{"timestamp":" 947986424088"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986424731","data":{"timestamp":" 947986424731"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986427522","data":{"timestamp":" 947986427522"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986427766","data":{"timestamp":" 947986427765"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986428439","data":{"timestamp":" 947986428439"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986429049","data":{"timestamp":" 947986429048"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986429652","data":{"timestamp":" 947986429652"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986430909","data":{"timestamp":" 947986430908"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986433728","data":{"timestamp":" 947986433727"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986434952","data":{"timestamp":" 947986434952"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986438411","data":{"timestamp":" 947986438411"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986439071","data":{"timestamp":" 947986439071"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986439935","data":{"timestamp":" 947986439934"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986440877","data":{"timestamp":" 947986440876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986442040","data":{"timestamp":" 947986442040"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986443409","data":{"timestamp":" 947986443379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" AKIMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986444294","data":{"timestamp":" 947986444294"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986445363","data":{"timestamp":" 947986445362"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986446539","data":{"timestamp":" 947986446538"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986447857","data":{"timestamp":" 947986447857"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIRARUA"," userResponse":" ALIIRARUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986448393","data":{"timestamp":" 947986448393"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986449003","data":{"timestamp":" 947986449002"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986451758","data":{"timestamp":" 947986451758"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986452823","data":{"timestamp":" 947986452822"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTUMA"," userResponse":" ALIMTUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986453586","data":{"timestamp":" 947986453586"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKONI"," userResponse":" SOKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986454374","data":{"timestamp":" 947986454373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986455305","data":{"timestamp":" 947986455304"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINDANO"," userResponse":" SINDANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986456218","data":{"timestamp":" 947986456218"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986456813","data":{"timestamp":" 947986456813"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" AWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986457583","data":{"timestamp":" 947986457582"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHONA"," userResponse":" KUSHONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986458136","data":{"timestamp":" 947986458136"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986458704","data":{"timestamp":" 947986458703"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986461784","data":{"timestamp":" 947986461782"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986462808","data":{"timestamp":" 947986462807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986463732","data":{"timestamp":" 947986463731"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINDANO"," userResponse":" SINDANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986464246","data":{"timestamp":" 947986464246"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986465134","data":{"timestamp":" 947986465134"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIWEKA"," userResponse":" KUIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986465855","data":{"timestamp":" 947986465855"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKIA"," userResponse":" KATIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986466511","data":{"timestamp":" 947986466510"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986466711","data":{"timestamp":" 947986466711"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986467212","data":{"timestamp":" 947986467212"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986467829","data":{"timestamp":" 947986467828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986471281","data":{"timestamp":" 947986471281"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986472114","data":{"timestamp":" 947986472114"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIENDA"," userResponse":" AKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986473063","data":{"timestamp":" 947986473062"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986474580","data":{"timestamp":" 947986474579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986475448","data":{"timestamp":" 947986475447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986476362","data":{"timestamp":" 947986476362"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986477050","data":{"timestamp":" 947986477049"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986477325","data":{"timestamp":" 947986477325"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986477755","data":{"timestamp":" 947986477754"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986480778","data":{"timestamp":" 947986480778"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIUNGA"," userResponse":" AKAJIUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986481389","data":{"timestamp":" 947986481389"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAO"," userResponse":" NAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986484504","data":{"timestamp":" 947986484504"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINDANO"," userResponse":" SINDANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986485626","data":{"timestamp":" 947986485626"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIANGUKA"," userResponse":" ILIANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986486331","data":{"timestamp":" 947986486331"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986487357","data":{"timestamp":" 947986487356"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" MFUKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986487677","data":{"timestamp":" 947986487676"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986488579","data":{"timestamp":" 947986488578"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOTEA"," userResponse":" KUPOTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986491762","data":{"timestamp":" 947986491762"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipowasili nyumbani alimwambia mamake kilichotokea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWASILI"," userResponse":" ALIPOWASILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986492776","data":{"timestamp":" 947986492776"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipowasili nyumbani alimwambia mamake kilichotokea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986494507","data":{"timestamp":" 947986494507"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipowasili nyumbani alimwambia mamake kilichotokea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986495289","data":{"timestamp":" 947986495289"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipowasili nyumbani alimwambia mamake kilichotokea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986496743","data":{"timestamp":" 947986496742"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipowasili nyumbani alimwambia mamake kilichotokea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986499246","data":{"timestamp":" 947986499246"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986499759","data":{"timestamp":" 947986499758"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986500794","data":{"timestamp":" 947986500794"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986501619","data":{"timestamp":" 947986501618"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJAO"," userResponse":" UJAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986502365","data":{"timestamp":" 947986502364"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IDUNGE"," userResponse":" IDUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986503121","data":{"timestamp":" 947986503121"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINDANO"," userResponse":" SINDANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986503538","data":{"timestamp":" 947986503538"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986504577","data":{"timestamp":" 947986504577"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986505539","data":{"timestamp":" 947986505536"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986506484","data":{"timestamp":" 947986506484"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986508826","data":{"timestamp":" 947986508825"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986509430","data":{"timestamp":" 947986509429"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986510634","data":{"timestamp":" 947986510633"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAELEWA"," userResponse":" NAELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986511978","data":{"timestamp":" 947986511977"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986512855","data":{"timestamp":" 947986512854"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986513053","data":{"timestamp":" 947986513053"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986513138","data":{"timestamp":" 947986513138"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986518480","data":{"timestamp":" 947986518480"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986524903","data":{"timestamp":" 947986524902"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f8dd9741-c08d-411e-9a09-6e82b0d76a75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986533989","data":{"timestamp":" 947986533989"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986536072","data":{"timestamp":" 947986536072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986538146","data":{"timestamp":" 947986538145"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986541389","data":{"timestamp":" 947986541388"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986543647","data":{"timestamp":" 947986543646"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986545825","data":{"timestamp":" 947986545824"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986548607","data":{"timestamp":" 947986548607"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986550754","data":{"timestamp":" 947986550754"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986552881","data":{"timestamp":" 947986552881"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986556007","data":{"timestamp":" 947986556007"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986558053","data":{"timestamp":" 947986558053"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986560095","data":{"timestamp":" 947986560095"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986563013","data":{"timestamp":" 947986563013"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986565273","data":{"timestamp":" 947986565272"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986567513","data":{"timestamp":" 947986567513"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986570583","data":{"timestamp":" 947986570582"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986572954","data":{"timestamp":" 947986572953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986575307","data":{"timestamp":" 947986575306"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986578449","data":{"timestamp":" 947986578448"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986580569","data":{"timestamp":" 947986580569"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986582745","data":{"timestamp":" 947986582745"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986585829","data":{"timestamp":" 947986585829"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986587960","data":{"timestamp":" 947986587960"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986590113","data":{"timestamp":" 947986590113"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986593326","data":{"timestamp":" 947986593325"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986595752","data":{"timestamp":" 947986595752"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986598194","data":{"timestamp":" 947986598193"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986601293","data":{"timestamp":" 947986601293"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986603568","data":{"timestamp":" 947986603566"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986605856","data":{"timestamp":" 947986605855"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986607823","data":{"timestamp":" 947986607823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986607906","data":{"timestamp":" 947986607906"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986614110","data":{"timestamp":" 947986614110"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 41441ffb-b521-49f6-94c3-297bd6dcce7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986625830","data":{"timestamp":" 947986625830"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986630644","data":{"timestamp":" 947986630643"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986632237","data":{"timestamp":" 947986632236"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986636531","data":{"timestamp":" 947986636530"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986638100","data":{"timestamp":" 947986638100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986641916","data":{"timestamp":" 947986641915"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" START_KULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986643664","data":{"timestamp":" 947986643664"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986645239","data":{"timestamp":" 947986645238"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986648784","data":{"timestamp":" 947986648784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986650351","data":{"timestamp":" 947986650351"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" KILIMANJARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986657319","data":{"timestamp":" 947986657318"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986658893","data":{"timestamp":" 947986658893"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986661695","data":{"timestamp":" 947986661695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986663265","data":{"timestamp":" 947986663264"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986666822","data":{"timestamp":" 947986666822"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986668388","data":{"timestamp":" 947986668388"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986670480","data":{"timestamp":" 947986670479"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986672037","data":{"timestamp":" 947986672037"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kofia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986676079","data":{"timestamp":" 947986676079"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kofia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986677654","data":{"timestamp":" 947986677654"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitenge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986680432","data":{"timestamp":" 947986680431"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitenge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986682005","data":{"timestamp":" 947986682005"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986684373","data":{"timestamp":" 947986684373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986685934","data":{"timestamp":" 947986685934"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986689586","data":{"timestamp":" 947986689586"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986691142","data":{"timestamp":" 947986691142"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986694092","data":{"timestamp":" 947986694092"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986695650","data":{"timestamp":" 947986695650"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986699442","data":{"timestamp":" 947986699442"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986700995","data":{"timestamp":" 947986700995"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986704583","data":{"timestamp":" 947986704583"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986706164","data":{"timestamp":" 947986706164"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986710727","data":{"timestamp":" 947986710727"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986712331","data":{"timestamp":" 947986712330"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" KITAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986717991","data":{"timestamp":" 947986717990"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986719581","data":{"timestamp":" 947986719581"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986723588","data":{"timestamp":" 947986723587"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986725141","data":{"timestamp":" 947986725141"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986728255","data":{"timestamp":" 947986728255"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986729806","data":{"timestamp":" 947986729806"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kikombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986733045","data":{"timestamp":" 947986733045"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kikombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986734651","data":{"timestamp":" 947986734650"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986737446","data":{"timestamp":" 947986737446"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986739054","data":{"timestamp":" 947986739054"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kalamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986741637","data":{"timestamp":" 947986741637"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kalamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986743253","data":{"timestamp":" 947986743253"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986743998","data":{"timestamp":" 947986743998"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986744100","data":{"timestamp":" 947986744100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 59eb6527-1736-4b4e-aad7-dc6059f5dd64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986757399","data":{"timestamp":" 947986757399"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 456649c0-e37a-48e6-8dac-26192ba4e273"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986760205","data":{"timestamp":" 947986760205"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 456649c0-e37a-48e6-8dac-26192ba4e273"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986760291","data":{"timestamp":" 947986760291"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 456649c0-e37a-48e6-8dac-26192ba4e273"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986778146","data":{"timestamp":" 947986778145"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 456649c0-e37a-48e6-8dac-26192ba4e273"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986788755","data":{"timestamp":" 947986788755"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 456649c0-e37a-48e6-8dac-26192ba4e273"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986817853","data":{"timestamp":" 947986817853"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 456649c0-e37a-48e6-8dac-26192ba4e273"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986817953","data":{"timestamp":" 947986817953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" af6baa72-ebaa-4f9c-a7c8-925dd6a72159"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986827024","data":{"timestamp":" 947986827024"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986827397","data":{"timestamp":" 947986827397"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986827880","data":{"timestamp":" 947986827880"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986828224","data":{"timestamp":" 947986828223"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986828627","data":{"timestamp":" 947986828627"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986829100","data":{"timestamp":" 947986829100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986829323","data":{"timestamp":" 947986829323"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986832504","data":{"timestamp":" 947986832504"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986832538","data":{"timestamp":" 947986832538"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986833252","data":{"timestamp":" 947986833251"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986833645","data":{"timestamp":" 947986833645"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986833951","data":{"timestamp":" 947986833950"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986834160","data":{"timestamp":" 947986834160"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986834375","data":{"timestamp":" 947986834375"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986834694","data":{"timestamp":" 947986834693"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986834926","data":{"timestamp":" 947986834925"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986838118","data":{"timestamp":" 947986838118"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986838531","data":{"timestamp":" 947986838530"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986841089","data":{"timestamp":" 947986841089"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986841296","data":{"timestamp":" 947986841296"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986841507","data":{"timestamp":" 947986841507"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986844987","data":{"timestamp":" 947986844986"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986848762","data":{"timestamp":" 947986848762"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986849785","data":{"timestamp":" 947986849785"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986852434","data":{"timestamp":" 947986852434"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986852807","data":{"timestamp":" 947986852807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986853290","data":{"timestamp":" 947986853290"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986853633","data":{"timestamp":" 947986853632"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986854035","data":{"timestamp":" 947986854035"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986854509","data":{"timestamp":" 947986854508"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986854732","data":{"timestamp":" 947986854731"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986857965","data":{"timestamp":" 947986857965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986857999","data":{"timestamp":" 947986857999"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986858725","data":{"timestamp":" 947986858725"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986859134","data":{"timestamp":" 947986859133"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986859427","data":{"timestamp":" 947986859427"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986859630","data":{"timestamp":" 947986859630"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986859823","data":{"timestamp":" 947986859823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986860136","data":{"timestamp":" 947986860135"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986860358","data":{"timestamp":" 947986860358"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986861798","data":{"timestamp":" 947986861798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986893344","data":{"timestamp":" 947986893344"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" da09c8a8-57fd-4930-9b48-e7efd5c2fba6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986893404","data":{"timestamp":" 947986893404"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" aadf87eb-0258-4964-93ca-991f0ebc80a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986899834","data":{"timestamp":" 947986899834"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" aadf87eb-0258-4964-93ca-991f0ebc80a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986907234","data":{"timestamp":" 947986907234"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" aadf87eb-0258-4964-93ca-991f0ebc80a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.99","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986913419","data":{"timestamp":" 947986913418"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" aadf87eb-0258-4964-93ca-991f0ebc80a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986918369","data":{"timestamp":" 947986918369"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" aadf87eb-0258-4964-93ca-991f0ebc80a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986925243","data":{"timestamp":" 947986925242"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" aadf87eb-0258-4964-93ca-991f0ebc80a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986938526","data":{"timestamp":" 947986938526"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 74e7807a-c798-4261-a325-8f3475245ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986945346","data":{"timestamp":" 947986945346"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 74e7807a-c798-4261-a325-8f3475245ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986945471","data":{"timestamp":" 947986945471"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" 74e7807a-c798-4261-a325-8f3475245ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:K..K.all.10.rand.say.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986966011","data":{"timestamp":" 947986966011"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f0f22b44-0e0b-45f8-b65f-021185695877"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_K..K.all.10.rand.say.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_k_ch"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:K..K.all.10.rand.say.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986973522","data":{"timestamp":" 947986973522"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f0f22b44-0e0b-45f8-b65f-021185695877"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_K..K.all.10.rand.say.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_k_ch"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:K..K.all.10.rand.say.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986980165","data":{"timestamp":" 947986980165"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f0f22b44-0e0b-45f8-b65f-021185695877"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_K..K.all.10.rand.say.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_k_g_r"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:K..K.all.10.rand.say.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986987742","data":{"timestamp":" 947986987741"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f0f22b44-0e0b-45f8-b65f-021185695877"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_K..K.all.10.rand.say.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_k_g_r"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:K..K.all.10.rand.say.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986994380","data":{"timestamp":" 947986994380"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f0f22b44-0e0b-45f8-b65f-021185695877"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_K..K.all.10.rand.say.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_k_z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:K..K.all.10.rand.say.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947986997021","data":{"timestamp":" 947986997020"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_042541"," gameId":" f0f22b44-0e0b-45f8-b65f-021185695877"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_K..K.all.10.rand.say.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_p_k_z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}